Excuse me, sir. How old were
you when you made your first million?
A million or billion?
Billion.
Billion? That was only recent.
A million when I was 24.
So you're a billionaire?
Yes, fortunately I am.
And what's your name?
Tony Robbins. How would you not know
that if you were at my home?
Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your yacht?
Yeah.
What did you do to
be able to buy a yacht?
I'm in the business.
How long have you been in the business?
A long time. Yeah, this far, a long time.
How much was this boat?
You want me to tell you
the good news or the bad news?
The bad news first.
The bad news is 120 million euros.
A hundred billion dollars?
Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your G-Wagon?
It is.
And how did you get rich? How
old were you when you became a millionaire?
And what line of business are you in?
I'm in the money business.
What do you mean?
Private equity.
What was the most amount of
money you made in a single year?
I have, at this point, 114 companies. We do $12
billion in business per year across a variety of industries.
I have had one business that generated
over $3 billion that I own personally.
What's the most fascinating thing you've
learned about people throughout your career?
Most people.
Let's go.
Dr. D, what's going on?
What's up, my guy?
What's going on?
All right, listen. You know the Paul brothers?
Jake and Logan Paul?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so, listen. Jake Paul's fight is tomorrow.
The weigh-ins are tonight.
I think I got you an interview with Jake.
Are you down?
You're talking about tonight?
Yeah.
We're up in Paul Beach.
I don't know, bro. You figure it out.
All right, all right.
Hey, guys. You guys need to go.
Yeah, we're part of the private property. We're
part of this. We're doing a video with Jake.
I understand. Well, without credentials,
I can't have you stay here.
I need you to get out of here.
I have to get credentials. He's right here, dude.
Sir, I have a question for you.
All right.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Guys, this is about to be one of
the most insane videos that you have ever seen.
And I'm not kidding because right
now, I'm standing in the millionaire's playground.
Scratch that. Billionaire's playground.
I'm out here in Paul
Beach, right up north of Miami.
And there's more billionaires that live
here than anywhere else on Earth.
And I'm going to be cold approaching multi-millionaires,
billionaires in the streets of Paul Beach today
to figure out how they got rich.
But that's not all.
Because I secured an interview out
here in Paul Beach with Tony Robbins,
the man who's behind the mindset
of all the billionaires that you know.
And he himself has made millions
of billions of dollars throughout his career.
So this video, like I said, is
about to be insane from start to finish.
So stay tuned until the end.
That being said, let's get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir. Sir, how old
were you when you became a millionaire?
Real quick. So I grew a channel to 18 million followers,
interviewing business owners all over the world to help the younger generation.
Excuse me, sir. Sir, how old
were you when you became a millionaire?
What line of business were you in?
How did you get rich that early?
Oh, you're talking to the right guy.
No, real quick, sir. So I grew a channel to 18
million followers, interviewing the most successful people to help the younger generation.
Well, I'm not anywhere near being a millionaire.
What line of business were you in?
I got to go.
All right, man. Have a good one.
Excuse me, sir. Sir, how old
were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm sorry?
How old were you when you made your first million?
They made their millions already.
Yeah. Wait, wait. How did
you make it that early, sir?
We're not doing anything.
All right, here. Run this one.
Excuse me, sir. How did you get rich?
I don't do these videos.
How did you get rich?
So real quick.
I've seen your videos.
Yeah.
It's cool.
So I've interviewed over 30
billionaires in the last four years.
What line of business were you in?
I don't do it.
Here's my question.
My next professional racing driver, you
can do the rest of the races.
You're a racing driver?
I was. Retired.
What was your name?
Jake Hoffman.
Jake Hoffman. One message for the
younger generation that could help them out?
You're good at what you do,
but I'm just trying to tell you.
You got to be persistent, man.
All right, you guys.
So the Palm Beach has been
insane to film it so far.
I can't get these people to stop and
give me a second to do an interview.
But look, I just got the word
that while we're in Palm Beach right now,
one of the biggest yacht owners meet
up is happening right now in this city.
So we're going to head over to it to go find
and interview yacht owners to figure out how they built their wealth
and got rich in the billionaire's
playground of Palm Beach, you guys.
So let's head over right now
and go see who we can find.
Guys, real quick.
I got to show you something right now.
So this book.
It's standing right behind me.
You can see it in the background.
Apparently, it was bought for over $100 million.
But I've got crazier news.
Apparently, the owner of that yacht, the person
that bought it is actually here right now.
And he's on the boat.
And we were told that any second now he could be coming out onto the deck and we can
actually go up and approach him to figure out what he did to be able to buy this thing.
I've got no idea what this person did.
I don't even know how you buy $100 million yacht.
But we're about to figure out super soon because
I'm not going to take no for an answer.
I'm not going to stop until I figure out what
he did to be able to buy this thing, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, is this your yacht?
Yes.
What did you do to
be able to buy a yacht?
I'm in the car business.
What business?
New car business.
I'll do cars.
You're in the car business?
Yeah.
How long have you been in the business?
A long time.
I've been in this business a long time.
How much was this boat?
You want me to tell you
the good news or the bad news?
The bad news first.
The bad news is 120 million euros.
$100 billion?
What was the most amount of money you've
made in a single year at your business?
$200 billion.
$200 billion?
Could I interview you for one minute?
I go all over the world interviewing billionaires
and the wealthiest people to help the younger generation.
Could I get a picture?
Can I get a minute with you for the channel?
The younger generation?
Yeah.
You want to come on?
Is that cool?
Thank you for having us on, sir.
How are we doing?
What's your name?
John.
What's yours?
I'm James.
Where are you from?
Originally Brooklyn.
I live in Florida now.
Yeah.
Now, I have one rule for all my interviews.
There's no holding back.
Could we give the younger generation the blueprint
on how to become successful in today's world?
Sure.
Let's make it happen.
How much are you worth today?
Big money.
Have you ever been over in business?
Oh, yeah.
Plenty of times I had people do it,
but you don't pay back, so we're .
Yeah.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
What made you want to go out
there and become such a successful entrepreneur?
I learned something in my life.
I don't know what the word no means.
You don't take no for an answer?
No.
Why not?
The people that doubted me, I look at them
and I say, you should never not believe what
I can do because here you are.
You're out looking to get in
and I won't let you in.
Have you ever been broke before?
No.
Never been broke before?
I don't want to be either.
What keeps so many people broke in today's world?
What happens with some people, they
make their thoughts bigger than their .
Break that one down.
No.
They do things really bigger than they should.
It's just so much food
you could put in your mouth.
Don't put too much food because you're going to choke.
How old are you now?
You look amazing for 78.
Are you still running companies today?
Oh yeah.
I work every day.
Are you serious?
What's keeping you so motivated?
Is it just the love and the passion you have?
I just love what I do.
I just feel I'm too young to retire
even though a lot of people think I'm crazy.
My father lived to 101 and
he worked until he was 100.
I just want to keep going.
I enjoy myself.
I get up in the morning.
I'm motivated.
I just want to keep doing things.
I'm still buying companies today.
You're still buying companies?
Yeah.
An hour ago, I had a guy who
pissed and I was buying one of his companies.
What type of company?
A North Carolina dealership.
As a multiple nine-figure entrepreneur, what's the
best financial advice you could give to
the younger generation?
I will tell you that a
lot of people hoard their money.
What I mean by that is they make the money
and they just want to see it in the bank.
Money sitting in the bank don't make you money.
In the early days, we used to get loan books.
They looked like chance books.
And I had so many loans out and
I made sure we paid them all back.
And then I started saying, I'm
not going to get no more loans.
I'm going to try and do everything with my money.
And that's what I did.
I put the money in the bank.
I put the money to use.
Buying businesses, buying boats.
So it's safe to say that
scared money does not make money.
Right.
Dangerous.
And do you believe in God?
I do.
How did you know God was real?
Look.
I'm looking at myself today.
I used to think I could fly
without wings, but I never tried that one.
No.
So you had someone there guiding you all along?
Yes.
I love that.
You've got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much for your time.
I really appreciate that.
Could I get your contact?
Yeah.
You want to come in for a sec?
You want to see inside the boat?
Yeah, for sure.
Come on, guys.
Awesome.
Wow.
And they're really special.
Very expensive.
This is my office.
That's my new plane I just bought.
Rami, you bought this for how much?
When we first bought it, we
bought it for about 90 something million.
Are you selling this boat right now?
No.
You're not?
What if I put up 121?
I got two offers already on the table.
One for 120 million euros and one for 130 million.
People could afford it.
But you know what?
Christmas and New Year's we spend on a boat.
I'm looking at a new boat right now.
I'm talking to a couple of shipyards.
I'm looking at an 80 meter.
This is 74.
Yeah.
And the criteria is I'm odd.
My birthday's odd.
I'm born in January 15th, 1947.
So if I buy a boat,
it's got to be an odd year.
So it'll be 2027.
So in 2027, I will have a new boat.
I ordered another new plane and
then I'm going to take it easy.
Can I give you guys
a coffee or water or anything?
I'll have a coffee for sure.
Yeah, I'll definitely have a coffee.
Okay.
Guys, we just interviewed an absolute mogul
on his 120 million dollar yacht, you guys.
And he just gave so
much amazing advice in that interview.
He even let us come on
and check out the yacht, man.
But look, as you can see, look,
we're back in Palm Beach right now.
We're going to come out here and
find some more millionaires and billionaires that live
out here, you guys.
So let's keep this thing rolling and
go see who else we can find.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, is this your G-Wagon?
It is.
And how did you get rich, man?
Like how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Yeah.
And what lot of business are you in?
I'm in the money business.
The money business?
What do you mean?
Private equity, investing in companies, loving it.
So how many companies do you own today?
Today, 82, 84 plus companies and growing.
And across all these companies, what was the
most amount of money you made in a single
year?
A lot.
Give me a range.
I don't know.
I have had one business that generated
over 3 billion that I own personally.
3 billion dollars?
3 billion dollars.
Now I got all over the world
to interview billionaires to help the younger generation.
Can I get a minute with
you for the channel real quick?
Sure.
Do you have kids today?
I do.
I have three teenage boys, 18, 17, 15.
Let me ask you this.
If you could instill one financial principle
into your kids before you leave this earth,
what will that be?
I always say to them, if you spend
a dollar, you have to go make two.
So realize once you spend that dollar, you've got
to go make $2 to get the dollar back.
Don't spend.
Discipline yourself to stack it up and then focus
on, as I tell them now, if you're not
studying compounding and where interest is,
the private equity game is so good.
You don't have to be a
genius to be in private equity.
Yes, you need some capital, but
that's why you want to save.
You've got businesses doing over $3 billion a year.
You're still building companies today.
You own 80 companies now.
Why still keep building businesses and
making millions and billions of dollars?
Why are you still-
Business is fun.
People are fun.
I think at the end of the
day, fulfillment is the number one deal.
You are very fulfilled by what you do.
You love it.
You get a high off of talking to people, right?
And you learn so much from it.
So I think-
We've made millions of dollars from it too.
Exactly.
But it comes with loving what you do.
You got to love what you do
and everyone will find what they love.
They just have to be willing to turn
over a million more rocks than most people.
Most people that you and I grew up with,
they just wouldn't even take the chance of turning
over five rocks for fear of what their name
may look like for trying three or four ventures
and falling on their face.
They're worried about what people think.
They're worried about what people think about them.
It's the biggest mistake you
can make in your early 20s.
How did you overcome that?
Because I'm sure you have people that doubt you.
I'll tell you a fast, funny story.
So before the internet, I was making
six figures a month in my mid 20s.
And so back then it was life changing, right?
But I was saving, saving, saving, saving.
I understood how to invest.
Back in that day, there was a phone book.
Never will forget, one day I'm looking at
this phone book and I'm looking in the mirror
and I'm like, you're the biggest liar.
I'm looking at myself in the mirror going,
here's a phone book with every first thing.
First name and last name within
a radius of where I live.
And so I started calling every first name I'd like.
I'd say, hello, David, so and so.
I can't remember where I met you, but I
wanted to give you some updates on my company.
And I started going through that and
it was a big game changer for me.
In my confidence level, I understood
the power of leaving voice messages.
So I think in today's world, the other thing
that I would tell all of you is your Rolodex
is your Rolex.
Your Rolodex is your Rolex.
And if you utilize-
That's deep.
I've never heard that before.
Yep.
I think everyone has all these contacts.
You've got all these friends, but what are
you putting in front of them that you feel
has value, that you're passionate about, and
that you feel is something that they need
to purchase?
If you say, trust me, order this,
you'll hug me later, you're on your way.
So it's true when they say that the
more hands you shake, the more money you make.
5 billion per sip.
You got rejected, I'm sure.
A million times.
Why did you not care about that?
Found and determined.
And I love what I was doing.
I thought it had a benefit to
everyone that I was reaching out to.
If you don't feel like
what you're putting your name on.
Your name to is beneficial
to others, you're wasting your time.
How important is it to follow up
in business with your customers, clients, whatever?
Great question.
I think when you think about fear of
loss, that's the awesome thing about follow up is
that you're just giving them updates on what's
going on with you, what's going on with the
company.
And so they know things are happening without them.
They know it's growing without them, or they
know that they're missing out on buying something.
Right.
So I've interviewed a lot of billionaires
and I've learned from them that the reason
why people go out of business is because they
don't know how to follow up with all their
clients.
There's a business I use.
It's called Go High Level.
And essentially what it does is
to automate your entire follow up process.
So even if you have different
businesses, different customers, different clients, it
literally automates the follow up process, reaches out
to all of them so you never lose
money or never lose a deal.
Absolutely.
I'm going to check it out today for sure.
Let's do it.
How old are you now?
How old do you think I am?
Fifty...
Fifty-four?
Fifty-five.
If me and you died tomorrow and you had
one more message to leave with the younger generation,
what would that be?
Give at least five to 10 compliments a day
to anyone that's in front of you, random people,
people that you don't know, people that you do
know, but make a habit every day to compliment
people and remember that we're all equal.
So don't think that you're better than anyone
else and when you stay humble, blessings come.
Got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much for your time.
Pleasure.
Thank you.
I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Yep.
Guys, we just interviewed someone who's making $3 billion
a year with a B and he is 100%
right, guys.
Look, if you don't master the
follow up, you do not master business.
Did you hear what he said
he's going to do after the interview?
He's going to check out Go High Level today.
And here's why that matters.
Look, I've interviewed hundreds of millionaires
and billionaires and they all said they're
all saying the exact same thing.
Most deals are not lost because
the product or service isn't good.
They're lost because nobody follows up.
And that is exactly why I use
Go High Level in my business every day.
Go High Level is the CRM
that automates your entire follow up process.
Now, if you don't understand why that's important,
listen, all of your texts, your emails, your
reminders, your entire pipeline is handled
automatically through Go High Level so you
don't lose any more deals.
And this is what
the most successful entrepreneurs understand.
Look, the only way to scale a business.
This into a multimillion dollar company is by using systems.
So someone who's making $3 billion a year
is focused on mastering the follow up and
building systems, then you should be too.
So waste no more time.
Guys, go down, click the link in the description
of this video to start your free trial using
Go High Level today and watch
your life and your business change.
Now, with that being said,
let's get back to the video.
Arch, guys, the time has now come.
Look, Miami and Palm Beach has
been insane like it always is.
But we are right now in route
to go and interview the legendary Tony Robbins.
Guys, look.
He's been making billions of
dollars of wealth throughout his career.
This guy's also coached billionaires, military
leaders, presidents of countries, you guys.
So today we're going to
be getting the secrets from him.
He's going to be mentoring us today on
how to become financially free and how to build
and create the life of your dreams.
So let's waste no more time.
Let's go meet the legend Tony Robbins himself.
Arch, guys.
So we just got to the destination where
we're going to be interviewing the legend himself,
Tony Robbins, man.
We're going to be walking through
the doors in any second now.
What's going on, my man?
How you doing?
Fantastic.
Who are we interviewing today?
Tony Robbins.
Let's go.
What's going on, Tony?
Hey, how you doing?
Good, man.
How are you?
Good to see you, man.
It's great to see you.
Thanks for coming by.
Nice to meet you, man.
We're happy to be here.
Who am I here with today?
Well, I think you know it's Tony Robbins.
You're at my home.
The legend himself.
Yes, sir.
Nice to meet you.
For those who don't know,
how did you make your billions?
I'm fortunate enough to have 114 companies.
We do over $12 billion
a year across massively different industries.
But it all started with understanding
human psychology because that's what drives all
of business and all of life.
I have one rule for everybody that I interview.
There's no holding back.
I give them the secrets and the blueprint on
what it takes to make it in today's world.
Can we make that happen?
I think we can make that happen.
Let's do it, my friend.
Let's take a seat.
Have a seat.
You got it.
There's a saying that I love.
If you don't come from a rich
family, a rich family can come from you.
You didn't come from a rich family.
What was Tony Robbins' turning point to financial freedom?
Tell us that turning point for those that don't know.
Actually, the earliest was when I was 11 years
old and we had no money and no food.
I had four different fathers.
My mom was a busy person.
All my fathers, unfortunately,
were not financially successful.
And we had a Thanksgiving when I was 11.
There was no money and no food.
When I say no food, we had crackers
and peanut butter, but not a Thanksgiving dinner.
And there was a knock at the door.
My parents were fighting and screaming at each other.
And this man delivered an entire turkey,
two whole bags of groceries for us.
I thought it would make my
father happy, but actually, he was...
Made him feel like he hadn't taken care of
his family, or he made himself feel that way,
and he left us.
So it felt like the worst day of my life.
But I took a different meaning from it.
Number one, there's food.
What a concept.
But number two is like,
this made me believe strangers care.
Because the person who delivered the food,
I still don't know who it was.
They didn't want credit.
They just knew we were having a tough time.
My entire life, people had said,
we grew in a really tough environment.
And it looked like everybody said, no
one gives a damn about anybody else.
But I had completely different evidence.
And so I thought, if strangers care about
my family, I'm going to care about them.
And so it launched me.
And I thought, someday I'll feed
at least two families, you know?
So at 17, I fed two, and
then I got to four, and then eight.
I had a little small company I grew, and
eventually I got to four million people a year.
And then 12 years ago, I decided I wanted
to provide a billion meals in the United States.
And so now that's grown.
My whole life has grown from this
focus on, how do you give more?
Not how do you get more?
Beyond the economics, it makes you feel
fully alive, like your life has real meaning.
So I'm very grateful for what I thought
was my worst day, became my best day.
At 17 years old, you found
one of your first mentors, Jim Rohn.
That's right.
You found out early on that success leaves clues.
And I recently interviewed Robert Herjavec.
And he told me that some of the most
bullshit advice that you hear all the time is that
people always tell you it's not
what you know, it's who you know.
Because he's saying that successful people aren't
necessarily going to give you the time
of day if you don't have value to offer
them, and a reason for them to connect and pour
into you.
So I want to ask you
for your advice to that young man.
Young person out there trying to
attach themselves to the right people.
They may not have a lot of credibility.
What would you do if you were them?
Your best networking tip to the younger generation?
I'll tell you what Jim Rohn taught me,
because it's the best advice I ever got.
I was 17 years old, and I went to
work for him because I loved what he was teaching.
I thought he was a genius in
business and philosophy and so forth, the strategy.
And so I went to one
day and said, I've got four fathers.
They were always broke.
They were good men.
Help me understand why we're broke.
Like no money at Thanksgiving.
I don't understand.
It doesn't seem fair that some school teacher
makes in those days $40,000, $35,000 a year.
And this billionaire hedge fund guy
makes a billion in a year.
And he said, Tony, listen to me.
He said, so I'll never forget.
He goes, we're all equal as souls.
You're right.
But we're not equal in the marketplace.
He said, if I asked you this, are there
people making money twice as much in money in the
same time?
I said, yeah, 10 times.
Yeah.
50 times.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How?
I don't know.
He said, it's very simple.
You have to become more valuable.
You have to do more for
others than anybody else in the marketplace.
And so in the beginning, when I went around
and try to get around people, we didn't have
the social media world that we do now where
you can do some of the things you do.
There was no way to get that out there.
But I went to work for people.
I worked as a janitor.
So I'd be around them.
I cleaned their desks and read
all their during the night, truthfully.
But then I gradually, as I kept adding value
to people, and that's the whole game of life.
I think the biggest challenge people are trying
to figure out what they're going to get.
But if you can figure out what you
can give, the doors will open for you.
But it has to be what people
need, not what you want to give.
What's the most fascinating thing you've
learned about people throughout your career?
Most people, rather than face their fear, they
come up with a story as to why their
life has not worked out.
I have ADHD.
It might be true, but so does Richard Branson.
He's done quite well, right?
Or, you know, I was abused as a child.
Well, so was I.
So were so many people, right?
Who cares, right?
That's just a story.
But most people, they'll come up with a
wall to protect them, but the wall that protects
you imprisons you.
And so you have to be fearless.
And fearless doesn't mean you don't have fear.
It means you fear less.
It means you take action anyway.
Courage doesn't mean you're not afraid.
Courage means you're scared to
shitless, but you do it anyway.
You have another summit that's coming up.
Yes, I do.
Once a year, I do
a summit for 1.3 million people.
And it came because of COVID.
And I was like, I don't
want people to be screwed over.
I'm used to doing stadiums.
And they started shutting down every stadium in the world.
So I built a studio, 50
foot high ceilings and 25 LED screens.
And I go for three days with people.
It's called Time to Rise.
You go to timetorisesummit.com, I believe it is.
And there's no charge.
All you got to do is show up
for about two and a half hours a day.
And I'll show you how to start your right.
Instead of hoping the year is going to go
right or sending a bunch of New Year's resolutions,
we'll show you how to put a plan
together that you can really implement and you'll have
a blast with it.
At 114 companies, there's a saying
that I love, concentration builds wealth, diversification
keeps it.
You weren't afraid to diversify
and go into different industries.
At what point do you think it's going to happen?
How can entrepreneurs should diversify?
That's a great question.
I think the worst mistake a parent can
make is they're a terrible parent, so they have
a second child, right?
And a third before they're really good at anything.
I see that with entrepreneurs often.
It's easy, it becomes fun to start something new.
I made that mistake early on myself.
I remember one time I was going to
a bunch of billionaire friends, I was coaching and
then I said, I really want
your help with all these opportunities.
And they like scolded the out of me
and said, look, Tony, you got to master this
thing before you go do these other 12 things.
And so I think you have to have
a certain level of mastery of business, economics and
so forth.
Otherwise you spread yourself.
Do things.
You're thin.
But once you get to move from being an operator
to an owner, like how could I run 114 companies
and be on the road and deliver and have
five kids and five grandkids and a wife that I
adore and so forth.
It's not possible unless you
really know how to leverage yourself.
So I know how to recruit great leaders.
I know how to scale things
and how to be extremely strategic.
And so if you can scale and you're
strategic and you hire the right people, that's how
you get the job done.
But running around and doing it yourself and
just the whole hustle culture, I believe hustle
cultures are useful thing to start things out.
But then you need strategy and I think
you've got to be really smart about not
dividing your interest and shield there.
How old are you now?
65, about to be 66.
Tony, if me and you died tomorrow and you
had one more message to leave with the younger
generation, what would that be?
I'd say be relentless.
Become the creator of your own life.
Don't settle for less than you can be or do
or create or give no matter how hard it gets.
Obviously it's hard.
There's nobody who's got great success in
their life or great fulfillment even more
importantly who hasn't been pushed
to the edge multiple times.
But it's the person that just won't give
up, who keeps moving forward and the person who's
found something they care about more than themselves.
I think that's the most important thing.
Okay.
If it's your kids or it's your family,
if it's your business, it's your mission, if
there's something you care about more than
you, you're going to have enormous energy
for the rest of your life.
If it's just about you, you don't
need that much to fulfill your basic needs.
And so you'll eventually burn out.
But if it's about something larger than yourself, man,
you know, I get up there and I go 12,
13, 14 hours at 66 years old and
people go, holy ****, I'm 24 or 25.
I can't keep up with this guy.
Right?
But where does that energy come from?
Yes, I work out like a
crazy person, but that's not enough.
It's psychic energy.
It's emotional energy.
It's the energy of knowing what you're doing matters.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for your time.
Your massive inspiration.
Thank you so much.
Blessings to you.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Dr. D, what's going on?
What's up my guy?
What's going on?
Listen, you know the Paul brothers?
Jake and Logan Paul?
Yeah.
Okay.
So listen, Jake Paul's fight is tomorrow.
The aliens are tonight.
I think I got you an interview with Jake.
Are you down?
You talking about tonight?
Yeah.
We're up in Paul Beach.
I don't know, bro.
You figure it out.
All right.
We can be there in
an hour, hour and a half.
Can we make it work?
I don't know.
We're going to make it happen.
Hey, we're about to go interview the legendary Jake Paul.
Thanks to Dr. D, man.
Look, we're about to make this happen right now.
Stay tuned.
We're on the way to Jake.
Come on.
All right, you guys.
We just got to the destination where
we're going to be interviewing Jake Paul.
You guys out here.
Mind me forward of you guys.
Come on.
Let me ask you a question.
What's up, man?
How you doing, bro?
Nice to see you, bro.
Hey, guys.
You guys need to go.
Yeah.
We're part of this.
We're doing a video with Jake.
I understand.
Well, without credentials, I can't have you stay here.
Okay.
Thank you.
He's right here, dude.
Cameras, backpacks, things like that.
Please take them off.
It's lame.
All right, you guys.
So any second now, that boy Jake
Paul is going to be coming out.
He's doing a weigh-in right now with Anthony Joshua, man.
He's got a fight tomorrow night.
He's got to drop some game to you guys, man.
This is crazy, guys.
It doesn't get any bigger
or better than this, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I had a question for you.
All right.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, I think I was like 20.
How did you get rich, man?
You made a lot of millions in your career.
Man, it was really getting a lot of
views back in the day from YouTube, brand deals,
and then selling merchandise.
Yeah.
Throughout your career, what was the most amount
of money that you've made in a single
year?
It'll probably be like this year, close to nine figures.
And that's net?
Yeah, net.
Yeah.
Always net.
Always count the net.
Don't count the gross, people.
You made millions off YouTube.
You made millions off of boxing and
now investing, man, in the business world.
What was your biggest driving factor to your success?
Yeah, I was always fascinated by Silicon Valley,
and I really started investing at 18 years
old.
I'm into startups.
I like people who are on the frontiers
of tech and changing the world and getting to
be around them and hearing their vision
and just helping them build their companies.
And so, yeah, investing is one of my biggest hobbies.
Yeah, it's going really well.
Tomorrow night, you're going to fight one
of the greatest fighters of all time.
I'm going to ask you the
same question I asked Tom Cruise.
Do you not fear anything?
No, I fear a lot of things, man.
But life is about fearing it and still
going after it, still pushing yourself, being outside
of your comfort zone and
pushing yourself outside of your boundaries.
That's where success lies.
So yeah, I definitely have fear going into the ring.
But I'm harnessing it to my advantage.
And what's your self-talk like in that moment?
Yeah, first and foremost, I thank God.
I know he wouldn't put me into
any moments that I wasn't capable of handling.
And then just belief in the vision,
seeing the knockout, seeing my hand raised, staying
positive.
If a negative thought comes up, I look at
it as like a car on the freeway passing by.
I acknowledge it, but I let it go.
And then just having fun, bro.
I literally just act like goofy and silly
all the time and dance around and talk and
just have fun.
And then when you're having fun, you're in
a flow state and there's joy and joy brings
more success as well.
That's something I've been dying to ask you.
You've been doubted more times than just about
anybody else, but you don't give a about
what anybody thinks about you.
Why did you not listen to those people?
Yeah, I know who I am
at the end of the day.
It's just me and God.
You're born alone, you die alone.
And a lot of these people are pushing
their own limitations that they have of themselves
onto you because they believe that they can't do it.
They're insecure.
They're the ones not chasing the dreams.
But not a single successful person.
And I think that's the
biggest thing that I've ever experienced.
I've never had a person who's
ever said anything hating on me.
So it's all the people, fighters, entrepreneurs
that always have great things to say.
It's the losers who try to
drag you down to their level.
And so I just focus on the positive always.
You've never met a hater that's doing better than you?
Exactly.
Facts, dog.
It seems like you found God recently.
How did you know God was real?
It started years ago through breathwork when
I first experienced the presence of God, probably
four or five years ago.
And since then, life has completely changed.
And being able to walk with faith and being
able to walk with God, it's been a great thing.
It's been a great experience.
I've always wanted to be able to walk
with faith and connect with God through meditation,
breathwork, and daily prayer.
There's always something that comes through a
lesson that needs to be worked on.
And it's been extremely helpful and changed my life.
And I'm able to walk into the ring
tomorrow without any fear because I asked Jesus to
take it from me.
And what's your name?
Jake Joseph Paul.
And how old are you?
I'm 28.
And your last message to the younger generation?
Find God, work hard, persevere, and practice discipline.
And don't give a what anybody else thinks.
Let's go.
You got amazing advice, man.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Congratulations, man.
Cheers, man.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, good to meet you, man.
Nice to meet you as well.
I love your stuff, bro.
Keep up the good work.
Hey, I got to do a video interview, man.
Yeah, we should do one maybe separate
than this, but we'll get one done eventually.
Can I get your contact?
Is that real?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, all right.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video, man.
We interviewed back to back Cody Robbins and Jake
Paul in the span of just a couple hours,
man.
My God, Jake gave a great interview, man.
I need you to stop what you're doing right now.
Like, subscribe for amazing content every
week because, guys, I'm telling you right
now, nobody's going to give you guys content like this.
Link it up with the people
that we're linking up with you guys.
Go down to the link in the description right
now because you can join the number one entrepreneur
community and network in the entire world
where you get access to eight, nine figure
and even billionaire entrepreneurs where you get
mentored from them every week on live
calls that we host.
We can't wait to see you on the inside.
With that being said, as always,
see you in the next video.